jandr.com 2013-05-01

# Privacy and Security | JR.com

  * • Privacy Policy
  * • Cookies
  * • Clear Gifs (Web Beacons)
  * • Advertising
  * • Loyalty Programs
  * • Information Sharing and Disclosure
  * • Legal Disclaimers
  * • Secure Shopping

## Privacy Policy

We at J&R take your privacy as seriously as you do. To help ensure your privacy, we use the most up-to-date encryption technology to keep your personal information as secure as possible. This includes your billing, credit card, and account information; none of this can be read as it travels to our system. We do **not** sell, trade, or otherwise share your personal information, such as name, email address, physical address, phone numbers, buying history, etc. without your permission, or except as otherwise provided in this Policy. You do not have to worry about receiving unsolicited email from other companies or individuals as a result of shopping, entering a contest or an auction at JR.com. If you would like to receive email regarding J&R Specials, leave the appropriate box checked during the Registration process, or fill in the sign-up form. Every email newsletter comes with a link to unsubscribe. We do, on occasion, send out an email announcement to inform our customers when we add a major new feature to our website; once again, those email addresses are not shared with anyone else. If you wish us to retain personal information (to make repeat shopping easier), you need to complete our registration process, which includes setting up a unique email address and password. To modify your personal information, you will need to click on " **My Account** ", and enter your email address and password. If you have any questions regarding our privacy practices, please contact [custserv@jr.com](mailto:custserv@jr.com). 

## Cookies

We require the Secure Sockets Layer ( **SSL** ) protocol and Session Cookies to be enabled on your browser in order to take advantage of many special features, such as registration and ordering, or you will not be able to place an order online. Session cookies allow us to hold items in your unique shopping cart, and to tell your shopping cart from that of another user. 

In order to assure that these services work, you may need to set-up your web browser. Here are some simple instructions; 

If you use Microsoft Internet Explorer, you can check and change the status of your SSL setting by clicking on Tools at the top of the browser, select Internet Options, click on the Advanced tab, scroll down to Security and make sure SSL is checked. You can check and change the cookies setting by clicking on Tools at the top of the browser, select Internet Options, click on the Security tab and then Custom Level, scroll down to Cookies and make sure it is enabled. 

If you use Netscape, you can check and change the status of your SSL setting by clicking on Security at the top of the browser, select Navigator on the left column, and make sure SSL 2.0 is checked under Advanced Security (SSL) Configuration. You can check and change the cookies setting by clicking on Edit at the top of the browser, select Preferences, click Advanced and make sure "Accept all cookies" is set. You can also use the procedure described above to block or restrict third-party cookies. However, if you do so, you will not be able to take advantage of many of the special features on our website. 

## Clear Gifs (Web Beacons)

We currently contract with several online partners to help manage and optimize our Internet business and communications. We use the services of marketing companies to help us measure the effectiveness of our advertising and how visitors use our site. To do this, we use clear gifs or web beacons and cookies provided by our marketing companies on this site. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. The type of anonymous, aggregate information we collect includes: pages viewed, searches, time spent on pages, first time visiting the site, and so on. By supplementing our records, this information helps us learn things like what pages are most attractive to our visitors, which of our products most interest our customers, and what kinds of offers our customers like to see. Although our marketing company logs the information coming from our site on our behalf, we control how that data may and may not be used. The information we collect through this technology is not personally identifiable; it does not tell us who you are. 

We use a third-party service provider to serve ads on our behalf across the Internet. They may collect anonymous information about your visits to our Web site, and your interaction with our products and services. They may also use information about your visits to this and other Web sites to target advertisements for goods and services. This anonymous information is collected through the use of a clear gif. If you would like more information about this practice and to know your choices about not having this anonymous information used by our third-party service provider, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>   
(Please note- some of the cookies that may show as "active" if you click on this link may be from other websites you have visited, not from J&R alone.) 

## Advertising

The ads appearing on this Web site are delivered to users by a reputable, third-party advertising partner(s). We share Web site usage information about users with such third-party advertising partners for the purpose of targeting our advertisements on this site. Such advertising partners may use cookies and clear GIFs on this site to enable them and their partners to recognize a user's cookie when a user visits this site and to serve ads to you based on your visit to this site or other sites on the Internet. The information that such advertising partners collect and share through this technology is not personally identifiable. For more information about these third-party advertising partners, or to learn more about the choices available to you regarding this anonymous information, please click here: <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>

## Loyalty Programs

When you come to the J&R website directly from a third-party website that operates a loyalty program, the third-party, loyalty program website will be able to access your individual transaction information. In order to track and properly credit your purchases, the loyalty program site will give you a unique identifier, such as a clear gif or cookie. Any purchases made at the J&R website while such a clear gif is active will be reported to the loyalty program site. J&R will report only non-personal information to these loyalty program sites, such as the date of the transaction, the product(s) purchased, and the amount spent. We will not report any personally identifiable information. However based on information which may have previously been collected from you by the loyalty program site, they may be able to personally identify you by combining the information they have gathered with the information sent by J&R. We suggest you review the privacy and data collection policies of these loyalty program sites. 

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Agents

We use outside shipping companies to fulfill orders, deliver packages and to schedule and perform product installations and provide such companies with the necessary order information in order for them to provide such shipping and delivery services. We use credit card processing companies and companies that provide fraud prevention services to verify and process credit card transactions, to provide fraud prevention services, and to bill you for goods and services, and provide such companies with order information, including credit card information, in order for such companies to provide such services. 

### Vendors

J&R will provide vendors with your contact information when requested to do so in connection with a product recall. J&R may sometimes provide certain vendors with your contact information or with other information when contractually required to do so. 

### Service Providers and Other Third Parties

We use a third-party service provider to distribute the J&R email newsletters. This third-party service provider is prohibited from using your personally identifiable information for any other purpose. 

When you use a third-party checkout on our site, certain of your information, such as name and billing and shipping addresses, may be provided by J&R to the third-party checkout to expedite the checkout process. When you use Bill Me Later on our site, J&R passes the order information to Bill Me Later in order for Bill Me Later to provide the financing for the sale. 

The product review content is provided by PowerReviews, and PowerReviews' policies, including its Terms of Use, Usage Agreement and Privacy Policy, govern the submission and use of all review content. 

## Legal Disclaimers

_We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law, such as when we believe that disclosure is necessary to comply with a subpoena, search warrant, court order, civil investigative demand, government investigation, or other compulsory process such as civil discovery. We also reserve the right to investigate, prevent, take action regarding, or report to law enforcement agencies, any activities that we believe to be unlawful, fraudulent, or a violation of our terms of use or policies, and to cooperate with law enforcement agencies investigating purported unlawful activities or suspected fraud. We also reserve the right to share certain personal information when we believe that such disclosure is necessary to protect the rights, property and safety of J &R or others. _

## Secure Shopping

At jr.com your order process is secured with the Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) protocol. SSL provides you with the freedom to shop online without the fear of your credit card information being stolen. This encryption compares to a combination lock that has several trillions of combinations. There are three ways that indicate whether you're on a secure web page: 

  1. All URL's (web addresses) that require and use an SSL connection start with **https:** instead of **http:**
  2. The key or padlock on your browser screen will become solid.
  3. Security Alert messages may popup while moving between regular and secure pages.

GoDaddy is a service that authenticates the integrity of this encryption method (see the GoDaddy logo on the screen during the order process).
